{
    "id": "1205c6f492694a279aff8c617a36b82a",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The shopkeeper will either return the money or ........................ the article.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "exchange",
                "exchanging"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4e843a56192646c7a87a9351e381be41"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................. he is poor, he will not pocket this insult.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2e9c99b251914690bfc5fb49baa0ce8d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Ram was a naughty boy who .......................... with his classmates.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "often quarreled",
                "was often quarreling"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "17608da007e14489813e4367105939ff"
        },
        {
            "question": "Women are said to be fond of flattery ....................... they are unaware of the shortfalls inherent in this weakness.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may be",
                "maybe"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "492f725a44414213b1d38009d4419789"
        },
        {
            "question": "Because you insist ...................... my going there, I shall do so.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "eabf9f842e824a59a6de2ff16bb98a50"
        },
        {
            "question": "Chandra Gupta, the founder of the Gupta Empire, ......................... for a pretty long period.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rolled",
                "ruled"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5fbbf6cde0814ec0ba0a496677cecec9"
        },
        {
            "question": "An ideal student works hard, ...................... his parents and teachers and has a good character.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "respect",
                "respects"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b6874d2b3032452884176c97800c6d7c"
        },
        {
            "question": "While I was having a walk in the park early in the morning, I stumbled upon a snake ...................... I took for a string.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e727ec150e494dc79b2b1d9f84728c73"
        },
        {
            "question": "All the members of Lalâ€™s family ......................... his youngest son are well-settled in their respective fields.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "exempt",
                "except",
                "expect"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dcc8f5fbd2834a618c8370a3780ea227"
        },
        {
            "question": "India, Pakistan and Bangladesh ..................... the Indian subcontinent.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "constitute",
                "constitutes"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "75dd72f7a6284ed594ef8ee39f3d93c2"
        }
    ]
}